http://www.news-spider.com/privacy.html

Hot Topics
User Name:
Password:
remember me
Forgot your password?
Not a member?
Privacy Policy
News-spider.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. We take privacy very seriously. Please read the following
to learn more about the privacy policy of news-spider.com web site and the related services offered herein.
News-spider.com offers links to various unrelated websites which are not within our control. These websites may have privacy policies that differ from ours. We are not
responsible, in any manner, for the privacy practices of such websites.
Types Of Information We Collect And How We Use It
IP Addresses
We use IP Addresses for statistical and system administration purposes. IP
addresses are anonymously logged to track a users session. We do not link IP
addresses with personally identifiable information. This means that a users
session will be logged but that user will remain anonymous to us. We can and
will us IP address to identify a user when necessary to enforce our terms of
service or protect our site, network, advertisers or users.
Cookies
We use session cookies to enhance the performance of certain services within
our site. This cookie does not contain any personally identifiable
information about users.
Contact Information
We collect contact information through various registration forms. This information is used to provide you with the services you requested.
Unique Identifying Information
We provide users of certain services with unique
usernames and passwords for use with those services. We use this
information for security purposes and to prevent unauthorized use, access,
alteration or misuse of your accounts and services.
Financial Information
We collect certain financial information (credit card information) from
users who order services from us. This information is used solely to
bill for services that you order.
With Whom Do We Share Your Information
News-spider.com will not sell, share or rent your personal information to anyone, for any reason.
We do not control the practices of our content providers. If you have questions about how our content providers use your information, please contact them directly.
Opting In/Out
News-spider.com provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing
information from us. You can send email to webmaster@news-spider.com to unsubscribe at any time.
Some services require registered participants to receive system announcements, invoices
or other official communications. Users of these services must receive these important notifications as a condition of service.
News-spider.com does not send unsolicited e-mail to its users for any reason.
Data Security and Data Access
News-spider.com has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.
Areas of the site, where valuable information is entered, are secured with 128 Bit SSL encryption - the latest in site encryption technology.
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect by editing your account information directly using the appropriate control panel on our website.
To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making changes or corrections to any of your personally identifiable information.
If you have any questions about the news-spider.com privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site,
please click here to view our contact information
News-spider.com may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.
Top Stories
Education
Lottery
Obituaries
Press Releases
Terrorism
Weather
World
U.S. Cities News:
© 2020 news-spider.com. All rights reserved.
All content is licensed under a Creative Commons Public Domain License, unless a source is quoted.
